Guide to the Images of Yale Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Alphabetical List of Individuals, Series I
  - Loomis, Dwight (Box 42, Folder 1553)
  - Loomis, Elias (Box 42, Folder 1554-58)
  - Loomis, Francis Engelsby (Box 42, Folder 1559-60)
  - Loomis, Henry Bradford (Box 42, Folder 1561-65)
  - Loomis, Hubbel (Box 42, Folder 1566)
  - Loomis, Osbert Burr (Box 42, Folder 1567)
  - Lord, Arthur Stone (Box 42, Folder 1567)
  - Lord, E. P. (Box 42, Folder 1567)
  - Lord, George DeForest (Box 42, Folder 1568)
  - Lord, John Clarendon (Box 42, Folder 1568)
  - Lord, Robert McC. (Box 42, Folder 1568)
  - Loree, James Taber (Box 42, Folder 1569)
  - Loree, Robert F. (Box 42, Folder 1569)
  - Loring, Daniel Alden, Jr. (Box 42, Folder 1570)
  - Lornsbury, Thomas R., Prof. (Box 42, Folder 1571)
  - Loth, Matilda (and family) (Box 42, Folder 1572-75)
  - Lou, Kia-chau (Box 42, Folder 1576)
  - Lough, Ernest St. George (Box 42, Folder 1576)
  - Loughbridge, William H. (Box 42, Folder 1577)
  - Loucks, Earl T. (Box 42, Folder 1577)
  - Lounsbury, Cooke (Box 42, Folder 1578)
  - Lounsbury, George Edward (Box 42, Folder 1578)
  - Lounsbury, Richard C. (Box 43, Folder 1579)
  - Lounsbury, Thomas R. (1859) (Box 43, Folder 1579)
  - Loutrell, Louis Frederick (Box 43, Folder 1580)
  - Love, C. R. (Box 43, Folder 1580)
  - Lovett, Augustus Sidney (Box 43, Folder 1581)
  - Lovett, Robert H. (Box 43, Folder 1581)
  - Lovejoy, Winslow (Box 43, Folder 1582)
  - Lovewell, John (Box 43, Folder 1582)
  - Low, N. G. (Box 43, Folder 1583)
  - Lowe, Paul Matthew (Box 43, Folder 1583)
  - Lowe, Walter (Box 43, Folder 1583)
  - Lowell, Robert (Box 43, Folder 1584)
  - Lowell, A. Lawrence (Box 43, Folder 1585)
  - Lowell, G. (Box 43, Folder 1585)
  - Lowndes, Lloyd (Box 43, Folder 1585)
  - Lowrie, Charles Nassau (Box 43, Folder 1586)
  - Luby, John Francis (Box 43, Folder 1586)
  - Lucas, George Clark (Box 43, Folder 1586)
  - Luccock, ? (Box 43, Folder 1586)
  - Luce Henry R. (Box 43, Folder 1586)
  - Luce, Henry Winters (Box 43, Folder 1587)
  - Luck, Jay (Box 43, Folder 1587)
  - Ludington, William Howard (Box 43, Folder 1587)
  - Ludlow, H. G. (Box 43, Folder 1588)
  - Lullock, R. L. (Box 43, Folder 1589)
  - Luquiens, Frederick B. (Box 43, Folder 1589)
  - Lusk, Dr. Graham (Box 43, Folder 1590)
  - Lusk, William Thompson (Box 43, Folder 1590)
  - Lussen, Thomas Asten (Box 43, Folder 1591)
  - Luther, Martin (Box 43, Folder 1591)
  - Lyck, Henry James Ten (Box 43, Folder 1591)
  - Lydgate, J. H. (Box 43, Folder 1592)
  - Lyman, Charles Northrop (Box 43, Folder 1593)
  - Lyman, Chester Smith (Box 43, Folder 1594-95)
  - Lyman, David Brainerd (Box 43, Folder 1596)
  - Lyman, Dean B., Jr. (Box 43, Folder 1596)
  - Lyman, Elisha Stiles (Box 43, Folder 1597)
  - Lyman, Eugene W. (Box 43, Folder 1597)
  - Lyman, Frank Clifford (Box 43, Folder 1598)
  - Lyman, Harold Thornton (Box 43, Folder 1598)
  - Lyman, Hart (Box 43, Folder 1598)
  - Lyman, Lauren D. (Box 43, Folder 1599)
  - Lyman, Oliver Ellsworth (Box 43, Folder 1599)
  - Lyman, Robert Hunt (Box 43, Folder 1600)
  - Lyman, Samuel Hinckley (Box 43, Folder 1601)
  - Lymon, Henry Hokixina (Box 43, Folder 1601)
  - Lynch, A. S. (Box 43, Folder 1601)
  - Lynde, Charles Rollin (Box 43, Folder 1602)
  - Lynde, William Pitt (Box 43, Folder 1602)
  - Lynes, Russell (Box 43, Folder 1603)
  - Lynn, Howley (Box 43, Folder 1603)
  - Lyon, George William Amos (Box 43, Folder 1603)
  - Lyon, Marcus (Box 43, Folder 1604)
  - Lyon, Stanley (Box 43, Folder 1604)
  - Lyon, Walter Dorsey (Box 43, Folder 1605)
  - Lytle, Andrew (Box 43, Folder 1605)
  - McAlpin, William (Box 43, Folder 1606)
  - McAndrew, George John (Box 43, Folder 1606)
  - McBirney, Hugh Johnston (Box 43, Folder 1607)
  - McBride, Malcolm Lee (Box 43, Folder 1608)
  - McCabe, Frank (Box 43, Folder 1609)
  - McCain, Charles Simonton (Box 43, Folder 1609)
  - McCall, C.H. (Box 43, Folder 1609)
  - McCall, Elmer S. (Box 43, Folder 1609)
  - McCall, John Oppie (Box 43, Folder 1610)
  - McCallum, A. B. (Box 43, Folder 1610)
  - McCance, William Hodge (Box 43, Folder 1610)
  - McCandless, Harry Darlington (Box 43, Folder 1611)
  - McCarthy, Donald C. (Box 43, Folder 1611)
  - McClellan, Edwin (Box 43, Folder 1612)
  - McClellan, George Eldredge (Box 43, Folder 1613)
  - McClellan, John (Box 43, Folder 1614)
  - McClelland, James Farley (Box 43, Folder 1614)
  - McClement, Arthur (Box 43, Folder 1615)
  - McClintock, Frank Thompson (Box 43, Folder 1615)
  - McClintock, Oliver (Box 43, Folder 1615)
  - McClintock, W. L. (Box 43, Folder 1616)
  - McClure, Archibald (Box 43, Folder 1616)
  - McClure, David (Box 43, Folder 1616)
  - McClure, William (Box 43, Folder 1617)
  - McCluskey, Audey M. (Box 43, Folder 1617)
  - McCollum, Dr. Elmer V. (Box 43, Folder 1618)
  - McConaughy, Donald (Box 43, Folder 1618)
  - McCook, Willis Fisher (Box 43, Folder 1618)
  - McCord, William (Box 43, Folder 1619)
  - McCormick, D. (Box 43, Folder 1619)
  - McCormick, Henry (Box 43, Folder 1619)
  - McCormick, James (Box 43, Folder 1620)
  - McCormick, [Joseph] Medill (Box 43, Folder 1620)
  - McCormick, Vance Criswell (Box 43, Folder 1621)
  - McCoy, Frank (Box 44, Folder 1622)
  - McCrea, James Alexander (Box 44, Folder 1622)
  - McCrea, S. H. (Box 44, Folder 1623)
  - McCullach, John Henry (Box 44, Folder 1623)
  - McCully, Charles G. (Box 44, Folder 1624)
  - McCully, Lawrence (Box 44, Folder 1624)
  - MacCurdy, Dr. George Grant (Box 44, Folder 1624)
  - McCutcheon, Chester (Box 44, Folder 1625)
  - McDermid, see: Blackwell (Box 44, Folder 1625)
  - McDevitt, Elmer W. (Box 44, Folder 1625)
  - McDonald, Frank Virgil (Box 44, Folder 1625)
  - MacDonald, Richard Hays (Box 44, Folder 1626)
  - McDougal, Myres Smith (Box 44, Folder 1626)
  - McDonough, John E. (Box 44, Folder 1626)
  - McDowell, Henry Clay (Box 44, Folder 1627)
  - McDowell, William Adair (Box 44, Folder 1627)
  - MacDuffie, Kurt H. (Box 44, Folder 1628)
  - McElroy, Joseph (Box 44, Folder 1628)
  - McEnerney, William (Box 44, Folder 1628)
  - McEvitt, Joseph L. (Box 44, Folder 1629)
  - Macfarland, Charles S. (Box 44, Folder 1629)
  - McFarland, Horace H. (Box 44, Folder 1629)
  - MacFarmer (Box 44, Folder 1630)
  - McGehee, George Thomas (Box 44, Folder 1630)
  - McGrath, William (Box 44, Folder 1631)
  - MacGregor, Donald (Box 44, Folder 1631)
  - MacGregor, Gordon (Box 44, Folder 1632)
  - MacGuffey, Kingsley Rick (Box 44, Folder 1632)
  - McGuire, John R. (1942) (Box 44, Folder 1632)
  - McHarg, Charles K. (Box 44, Folder 1632)
  - McHose, James (Box 44, Folder 1632)
  - McIntire, Albert W. (Box 44, Folder 1632)
  - McIntosch, Clyde (Box 44, Folder 1633)
  - Macintosh, Douglas C. (Box 44, Folder 1633)
  - McIntosh, James (Box 44, Folder 1633)
  - Mack, John (Box 44, Folder 1634)
  - Mackall, [Alexander] Lawton (Box 44, Folder 1635)
  - McKay, Edward DeCost (Box 44, Folder 1635)
  - MacKay, John James (Box 44, Folder 1636)
  - McKay, Robert Wilfred (Box 44, Folder 1636)
  - McKee, James Henry (Box 44, Folder 1637)
  - McKee, Oliver (Box 44, Folder 1637)
  - McKee, William James (Box 44, Folder 1637)
  - MacKenzie, Kenneth (Box 44, Folder 1638)
  - McKenzie, William (Box 44, Folder 1638)
  - MacKenzie, William Douglas (Box 44, Folder 1639)
  - McKeon, John L. (Box 44, Folder 1639)
  - McKim, Winthrop (Box 44, Folder 1639)
  - McKinlay, Thomas E. (Box 44, Folder 1640)
  - McKinley, William (Box 44, Folder 1640)
  - McKinney, Edward Pascal (Box 44, Folder 1641)
  - McKinney, William Allison (Box 44, Folder 1641)
  - MacKinnon, Clinton N. (Box 44, Folder 1642)
  - McKissack, Alexander Cogle (Box 44, Folder 1642)
  - McKnight, Everett James (Box 44, Folder 1643)
  - McKnight Robert Johnson (Box 44, Folder 1643)
  - McLain, Bernard Francis (Box 44, Folder 1644)
  - McLane, Guy Richards (Box 44, Folder 1644)
  - McLane, James Woods (Box 44, Folder 1645)
  - MacLane, Saunders (Box 44, Folder 1645)
  - McLaughlin, E. T. [?] (Box 44, Folder 1646)
  - McLaughlin, Thomas M. (Box 44, Folder 1647)
  - Maclean, Paul R. (Box 44, Folder 1648)
  - Macleish, Archibald (Box 44, Folder 1648)
  - MacLellan, George Boardman (Box 44, Folder 1649)
  - McMillan, Harvey R. (Box 44, Folder 1649)
  - McMillan, Thayer (Box 44, Folder 1649)
  - McMillan, William Charles (Box 44, Folder 1650)
  - McMurray, Clarence Fake (Box 44, Folder 1650)
  - McMurtrie, Rudolph (Box 44, Folder 1651)
  - McNamee, Daniel Vincen (Box 44, Folder 1651)
  - McNeil, Rallon (Box 44, Folder 1651)
  - McNeille, Robert George Stephen (Box 44, Folder 1652)
  - McNought, Andrew J. (Box 44, Folder 1652)
  - Macomb, Montgomery Meigs (Box 44, Folder 1653)
  - Macomber, Edwin (Box 44, Folder 1653)
  - McQuaid, Henry Pierre (Box 44, Folder 1653)
  - McVeagh, Franklin [MacVeagh] (Box 44, Folder 1654)
  - MacVeagh, Wayne (Box 44, Folder 1655-56)
  - Ma, Yin Ch"u (Box 44, Folder 1657)
  - Mabbatt, Richard Holloway (Box 44, Folder 1657)
  - Mabry, Harry Cooper (Box 44, Folder 1657)
  - Maddox, John Lee (Box 44, Folder 1658)
  - Magee, John A. (Box 44, Folder 1658)
  - Magee, John Gillespie (Box 44, Folder 1658)
  - Magee, Wm. Conner (Box 44, Folder 1659)
  - Magill, Seagrove William (Box 44, Folder 1659)
  - Magill, William Alexander (Box 44, Folder 1660)
  - Magruder, Benjamin Drake (Box 44, Folder 1660)
  - Maher, Edward (Box 44, Folder 1661)
  - Maher, James Stephen (Box 44, Folder 1661)
  - Mahoney, J. O. (Box 44, Folder 1661)
  - Mailliard, William S. (Box 44, Folder 1661)
  - Maines, Lawrence Herbert (Box 44, Folder 1662)
  - MaKuen, George Hudson (Box 44, Folder 1662)
  - Malcham, Charles O. (Box 44, Folder 1662)
  - Male, Francis P. (Box 44, Folder 1663)
  - Mallory, Charles Henry (Box 44, Folder 1663)
  - Mallory, William Neely (Box 44, Folder 1663)
  - Maltbie, William Mills (Box 44, Folder 1664)
  - Maltzberger, H. (Box 44, Folder 1664)
  - Manice, Edward Augustin (Box 44, Folder 1665)
  - Manierre, George (Box 44, Folder 1666)
  - Mann, Paul F. (Box 44, Folder 1666)
  - Mann, Richard Hess (Box 44, Folder 1666)
  - Manning, John Wesley (Box 44, Folder 1667)
  - Mansfield, B. (Box 44, Folder 1667)
  - Mansfield, Harvey C. (Box 44, Folder 1667)
  - Mansfield, Howard (Box 45, Folder 1668)
  - Mansfield, Jared (Box 45, Folder 1669)
  - Mansfield, Richard (Box 45, Folder 1670)
  - Manson, Aeneos (Box 45, Folder 1670)
  - Maples, J. W. (Box 45, Folder 1670)
  - Maplesden, Raymond J. (Box 45, Folder 1671)
  - Marcy, Dwight (Box 45, Folder 1671)
  - Marcy, Virgil (Box 45, Folder 1671)
  - Markert, Clement L. (Box 45, Folder 1672)
  - Marks, Frederick (Box 45, Folder 1673)
  - Marmaduke, Vincent (Box 45, Folder 1673)
  - de la Mare, Walter (Box 45, Folder 1674)
  - Marr, Evelyn Dillon (Box 45, Folder 1674)
  - Marsh, Charles Clark (Box 45, Folder 1674)
  - Marsh, Charles Othneil (Box 45, Folder 1674)
  - Marsh, Egbert (Box 45, Folder 1675)
  - Marsh, Frank Thompson (Box 45, Folder 1675)
  - Marsh, Frank Wanzer (Box 45, Folder 1675)
  - Marsh, Frederick (Box 45, Folder 1676)
  - Marsh, George B. (Box 45, Folder 1676)
  - Marsh, Howard Denham (Box 45, Folder 1676)
  - Marsh, John (Box 45, Folder 1677)
  - Marsh, Othniel C. (Box 45, Folder 1678-85)
  - Marsh, Valentine (Box 45, Folder 1686)
  - Marshall (Box 45, Folder 1686)
  - Marshall, Dr. Carter E. (Box 45, Folder 1686)
  - Marshall, James (Box 45, Folder 1687)
  - Marshall, John Ellis (Box 45, Folder 1688)
  - Marshall, John Porter (Box 45, Folder 1688)
  - Martell, Eldred (Box 45, Folder 1688)
  - Martin, Albert Cobb (Box 45, Folder 1689)
  - Martin, Clyde (Box 45, Folder 1689)
  - Martin, George Edward (Box 45, Folder 1689)
  - Martin, Newell (Box 45, Folder 1689)
  - Martin, Richard Denberthy, Jr (Box 45, Folder 1690)
  - Martin, Thor (Box 45, Folder 1690)
  - Martin, Winfred Robert (Box 45, Folder 1691)
  - Martyn, Sanford S. (Box 45, Folder 1691)
  - Martz, Louis (Box 45, Folder 1692)
  - Marvel, Jack (Box 45, Folder 1692)
  - Marvin, Joseph Howard (Box 45, Folder 1693)
  - Masaryk, Jan (Box 45, Folder 1693)
  - Masefield, John (Box 45, Folder 1693)
  - Mason, Frank Tucker (Box 45, Folder 1694)
  - Mason, Frederick R. (Box 45, Folder 1694)
  - Mason, Jeremiah (Box 45, Folder 1695)
  - Mason, Lawrence (Box 45, Folder 1695)
  - Massey, George Bragg (Box 45, Folder 1696)
  - Masters, Basil E (Box 45, Folder 1696)
  - Mather, Henry Frank (Francis)? (Box 45, Folder 1697)
  - Mather, Samuel Livingston (Box 45, Folder 1698)
  - Mathews, Charles Thompson (Box 45, Folder 1698)
  - Mathews, Harold Chauncey (Box 45, Folder 1698)
  - Mathews, Robert Elden (Box 45, Folder 1698)
  - Mathewson, Arthur (Box 45, Folder 1699)
  - Mathewson, Champion Herbert (Box 45, Folder 1699)
  - Matson, William L. (Box 45, Folder 1699)
  - Matthews, James Brander (Box 45, Folder 1700)
  - Matthews, James Thomas (Box 45, Folder 1701)
  - Matthews, Joseph Lee (Box 45, Folder 1701)
  - Matthiessen, Francis Otto (Box 45, Folder 1702)
  - Maudner, Elwood R. (Box 45, Folder 1702)
  - Mauther, Howard (Box 45, Folder 1702)
  - Maxson, Louis William (Box 45, Folder 1702)
  - Maxwell, George (Box 45, Folder 1703)
  - Maxwell, Henry Ziegler (Box 45, Folder 1703)
  - Maxwell, William (Box 45, Folder 1703)
  - May, Georges (Box 45, Folder 1703)
  - May, Mark Arthur (Box 45, Folder 1703)
  - May, Samuel C. (Box 46, Folder 1704)
  - Mayer, Lloyd O. (Box 46, Folder 1704)
  - Maynard, Robert Peachy (Box 46, Folder 1705)
  - Mayo, William Carrington (Box 46, Folder 1705)
  - Mead, Charles Abernathy (Box 46, Folder 1705)
  - Mead, Charles Dickey (Box 46, Folder 1706)
  - Mead, Edwin H. (Box 46, Folder 1706)
  - Mead, George G. (Box 46, Folder 1706)
  - Mead, George Houk, Jr. (Box 46, Folder 1707)
  - Mead, Ralph Adolph (Box 46, Folder 1707)
  - Mead, Roderick F. (Box 46, Folder 1707)
  - Mead, Walter Longworthy (Box 46, Folder 1708)
  - Means, David McGregor (Box 46, Folder 1708)
  - Mears, Richard Andrew (Box 46, Folder 1709)
  - Meek, John Burgess (Box 46, Folder 1709)
  - Meeker, David Magie (Box 46, Folder 1709)
  - Meeks, Everett U. (Box 46, Folder 1709)
  - Meese, Edwin III (Box 46, Folder 1710)
  - Meigs, Charles Edward (Box 46, Folder 1710)
  - Meigs, John (Box 46, Folder 1710)
  - Meigs, Josiah (Box 46, Folder 1710)
  - Meigs, Return J. (Box 46, Folder 1711)
  - Meikle, Frederick Clinton, Jr. (Box 46, Folder 1711)
  - Melance, Thomas (Box 46, Folder 1711)
  - Melville, Grevis W. (Box 46, Folder 1712)
  - Mendel, Lafayette B. (Box 46, Folder 1712)
  - Mendell, Clarence W. (Box 46, Folder 1713)
  - Mendenhall, Thomas (Box 46, Folder 1714)
  - Menderson, Nathan (Box 46, Folder 1714)
  - Mengal, Edwin P. (Box 46, Folder 1714)
  - Menton, Denis (Box 46, Folder 1715)
  - Menzel, Sauthard (Box 46, Folder 1715)
  - Mercer, George Wyllie (Box 46, Folder 1716)
  - Merchant, Henry S. (Box 46, Folder 1716)
  - Meredins, Alvin A. (Box 46, Folder 1716)
  - Mergen, Francois (Box 46, Folder 1717)
  - Merriam, Alexander Ross (Box 46, Folder 1717)
  - Merriam, James Fiske (Box 46, Folder 1717)
  - Merrifield, Mark Edward (Box 46, Folder 1718)
  - Merrifield, Webster (Box 46, Folder 1718)
  - Merrill, Helen A. (Box 46, Folder 1718)
  - Merrill, Selah (Box 46, Folder 1719)
  - Merrimay [?] (Box 46, Folder 1719)
  - Merritt, Edwin Albert (Box 46, Folder 1720)
  - Merritt, Henry N. (Box 46, Folder 1720)
  - Merritt, Schuyler (Box 46, Folder 1721)
  - Merriwell, Frank (Box 46, Folder 1722)
  - Merwin, Henry Warner (Box 46, Folder 1723)
  - Merwin, Samuel (Box 46, Folder 1723)
  - Messinger, Charles Raymond (Box 46, Folder 1723)
  - Metcalfe, Louis Rochat (Box 46, Folder 1724)
  - Metcalfe, James Stetson (Box 46, Folder 1724)
  - Mettler, William Maurice (Box 46, Folder 1724)
  - Metzger, Simon Charles (Box 46, Folder 1725)
  - Meyer, Cord (Box 46, Folder 1725)
  - Meyer, Eugene Isaac, Jr. (Box 46, Folder 1726)
  - Meyer, Henry (Box 46, Folder 1726)
  - Meyer, John (Box 46, Folder 1727)
  - Meyer, Walter H. (Box 46, Folder 1727)
  - Meyers, William Koontz (Box 46, Folder 1727)
  - Middlebrook, R. B. (Box 46, Folder 1727)
  - Middleton, John Cavarly (Box 46, Folder 1727)
  - Mika, Gaza Henry (Box 46, Folder 1728)
  - Miles, Daniel Augustus (Box 46, Folder 1728)
  - Miles, Egbert (Box 46, Folder 1729)
  - Milholland, Robert J. (Box 46, Folder 1730)
  - Millan, Edward Nesbitt (Box 46, Folder 1730)
  - Millard, James Slade (Box 46, Folder 1730)
  - Miller, Alanson Douglas (Box 46, Folder 1731)
  - Miller, Alfred Bolivar (Box 46, Folder 1731)
  - Miller, Charles Sumner (Box 46, Folder 1732-33)
  - Miller, Deane (Box 46, Folder 1734)
  - Miller, Edward T. (Box 46, Folder 1734)
  - Miller, Elisha Wright (Box 46, Folder 1734)
  - Miller, Francis (Box 46, Folder 1735)
  - Miller, George Douglas (Box 46, Folder 1736)
  - Miller, [Gerald] E. (Box 46, Folder 1737)
  - Miller, Harold Bourne (Box 46, Folder 1737)
  - Miller, Henderson H. (Box 46, Folder 1738)
  - Miller, Hiram Allen (Box 46, Folder 1738)
  - Miller, James E1y (Box 46, Folder 1738)
  - Miller, Jesse Wright (Box 46, Folder 1739)
  - Miller, John Jacob (Box 46, Folder 1739)
  - Miller, John Milton (Box 46, Folder 1739)
  - Miller, John Perry (Box 46, Folder 1740)
  - Miller, Joseph A. (Box 46, Folder 1740)
  - Miller, Matthew (Box 46, Folder 1740)
  - Miller, Ogden (Box 46, Folder 1741)
  - Miller, Phineas (Box 46, Folder 1741)
  - Miller, Richard White (Box 46, Folder 1741)
  - Miller, Robert Reitzell (Box 46, Folder 1742)
  - Miller, Seton (Box 46, Folder 1742)
  - Miller, Theodore Westwood (Box 46, Folder 1742)
  - Miller, William Cammack (Box 46, Folder 1743)
  - Miller, William Frederick (Box 46, Folder 1743)
  - Miller, William H (Box 46, Folder 1743)
  - Milles, Walter (Box 46, Folder 1744)
  - Milliken, Arthur (Box 46, Folder 1744)
  - Milner, Carl (Box 46, Folder 1744)
  - Mills, Ballinger (Box 46, Folder 1745)
  - Mills, Edward Milo (Box 46, Folder 1745)
  - Millspaugh, Francis C. (Box 46, Folder 1746)
  - Milstead, Century (Box 46, Folder 1746)
  - Miner, Thomas (Box 46, Folder 1747)
  - Minnig, Harley D. (Box 46, Folder 1747)
  - Minnigerode, Meade (Box 46, Folder 1748)
  - Minor, Charles W. (Box 46, Folder 1748)
  - Minor, Israel (Box 46, Folder 1748)
  - Minor, Samuel (Box 46, Folder 1749)
  - Minor, Solomon C. (1873) (Box 46, Folder 1749)
  - Minor, William Thomas (Box 46, Folder 1750)
  - Mintie, Robert Louis (Box 46, Folder 1751)
  - Minton, Sherman (Box 46, Folder 1751)
  - Mintz, Jacqueline Wei (Box 46, Folder 1751)
  - Mitchell, Charles Langon (Box 47, Folder 1752)
  - Mitchell, Donald Grant (Box 47, Folder 1753-54)
  - Mitchell, Elisha (Box 47, Folder 1755)
  - Mitchell, Helen Swift (Box 47, Folder 1755)
  - Mitchell, James B. (Box 47, Folder 1755)
  - Mitchell, John Grant (Box 47, Folder 1756)
  - Mitchell, John Hanson (Box 47, Folder 1757)
  - Mitchell, Walter Louis (Box 47, Folder 1757)
  - Mitsukuri, Kakichi (Box 47, Folder 1757)
  - Mixter, George Weber (Box 47, Folder 1758)
  - Mixter, William G. (Box 47, Folder 1759)
  - Mochary, Denis Paul Cornelius Stephen (Box 47, Folder 1760)
  - Moen, W. M. (Box 47, Folder 1760)
  - Moffat, Douglas M. (Box 47, Folder 1760)
  - Moffet, T. S. (Box 47, Folder 1760)
  - Moir, Stuart (Box 47, Folder 1760)
  - Moltz, A. (Box 47, Folder 1760)
  - Montegue, N. Thayer (Box 47, Folder 1761)
  - Montgomery, Frank D. (Box 47, Folder 1761)
  - Montgomery, Roger E. (Box 47, Folder 1761)
  - Mooney, John Davenport (Box 47, Folder 1761)
  - Moore, E. C. (Box 47, Folder 1762)
  - Moore, Edward S. (Box 47, Folder 1762)
  - Moore, Frank D. (Box 47, Folder 1762)
  - Moore, F. W. (Box 47, Folder 1762)
  - Moore, Franklin, Sr. (Box 47, Folder 1763)
  - Moore, George W. (Box 47, Folder 1763)
  - Moore, Hobart (Box 47, Folder 1763)
  - Moore, James William (Box 47, Folder 1763)
  - Moore, John B. (Box 47, Folder 1763)
  - Moore, Kate Leader (Box 47, Folder 1763)
  - Moore, Lawrence C. (Box 47, Folder 1764)
  - Moore, Louis F. (Box 47, Folder 1764)
  - Moore, Malcolm (Box 47, Folder 1764)
  - Moore, Nathaniel Schuyler (Box 47, Folder 1764)
  - Moore, Rollin D. (Box 47, Folder 1765)
  - Moore, William C. (Box 47, Folder 1765)
  - Moore, William Underhill (Box 47, Folder 1765)
  - Moore, Samuel Merrill (Box 47, Folder 1765)
  - Moorehead, John (Box 47, Folder 1765)
  - Morden, William (Box 47, Folder 1766)
  - More, Elawson Carry (Box 47, Folder 1767)
  - Morehouse, David Ogden (Box 47, Folder 1767)
  - Morgan, George Norris (Box 47, Folder 1768)
  - Morgan, Herbert M. (Box 47, Folder 1768)
  - Morgan, James P. (Box 47, Folder 1769)
  - Morgan, Joseph Richard (Box 47, Folder 1769)
  - Morgan, William Dare (Box 47, Folder 1770)
  - Moriarty, Frank & [Mrs.] (Box 47, Folder 1770)
  - Morison, Tom (Box 47, Folder 1770)
  - Morning, Ober (Box 47, Folder 1770)
  - Morris, Charles Newton (Box 47, Folder 1770)
  - Morris, Edward B. (Box 47, Folder 1771)
  - Morris, Edward P. (Box 47, Folder 1771)
  - Morris, Elisabeth (Woodbridge) (Box 47, Folder 1771)
  - Morris, John Moses (Box 47, Folder 1771)
  - Morris, Leo (Box 47, Folder 1772)
  - Morris, Lewis (Box 47, Folder 1772)
  - Morris, Luzou Burritt (Box 47, Folder 1772)
  - Morris, Newbold (Box 47, Folder 1773)
  - Morris, Robert Clark (Box 47, Folder 1773)
  - Morris, Stewart Edward (Box 47, Folder 1773)
  - Morrison, Samuel B. (Box 47, Folder 1774)
  - Morrogh, Charles Augustine (Box 47, Folder 1775)
  - Morrow, Samuel Roseburgh (Box 47, Folder 1775)
  - Morse, Arthur Henry (Box 47, Folder 1776)
  - Morse, Bennett W. (Box 47, Folder 1777)
  - Morse, Charles James (Box 47, Folder 1777)
  - Morse, Edwin Kirtland (Box 47, Folder 1778)
  - Morse, Huntington Tomlinson (Box 47, Folder 1779)
  - Morse, Jedidiah (Box 47, Folder 1780)
  - Morse, Jedidiah (and family) (Box 47, Folder 1781)
  - Morse, Jedidiah (residence of) (Box 47, Folder 1782)
  - Morse, Leonard Fisk (Box 47, Folder 1783)
  - Morse, Oliver C. (Box 47, Folder 1784)
  - Morse, Richard C. (and family) (Box 47, Folder 1785)
  - Morse, Samuel F. B. (and family) (Box 47, Folder 1786)
  - Morse Family (Box 47, Folder 1787)
  - Morse, Jedidiah (Box 47, Folder 1787)
  - Morse, Lucretia Pickering (Box 47, Folder 1787)
  - Morse, Richard Cary (Box 47, Folder 1787)
  - Morse, Samuel Finlay Brown (Box 47, Folder 1787)
  - Morse, Sidney Edwards (Box 47, Folder 1787)
  - Morse, Oliver Cromwell (Box 47, Folder 1788)
  - Morse, Richard Carey (Box 47, Folder 1788)
  - Morse, Sidney Edwards (Box 47, Folder 1788)
  - Morse, William Henry (Box 47, Folder 1788)
  - Morse, Samuel Finlay Breese (Box 47, Folder 1789)
  - Morse, Samuel Finlay Brown (Box 47, Folder 1789)
  - Morse, Wayne (Box 48, Folder 1790)
  - Morse, William H. (Box 48, Folder 1791)
  - Mosel, George S. (Box 48, Folder 1792)
  - Moseley, Spencer (Box 48, Folder 1792)
  - Morsell, Samuel R. (Box 48, Folder 1793)
  - Morton, Lyman Joseph (Box 48, Folder 1793)
  - Moses, Robert (Box 48, Folder 1794)
  - Mosle, Augustus Henry (Box 48, Folder 1794)
  - Moulton, Barron Clinton (Box 48, Folder 1795)
  - Mountjoy, Plato (Box 48, Folder 1795)
  - Mower, E. (Box 48, Folder 1796)
  - Moyer, John (Box 48, Folder 1796)
  - Mtimkulu, D. G. S. (Box 48, Folder 1797)
  - Mueller, Addison (Box 48, Folder 1798)
  - Mueller, Michael Joseph (Box 48, Folder 1798)
  - Muir, John (Box 48, Folder 1799)
  - Mulford, Elisha (Box 48, Folder 1800)
  - Mulford, Walter (Box 48, Folder 1800)
  - Mulkey, Marion F. (Box 48, Folder 1801)
  - Muller, Louis J. (Box 48, Folder 1801)
  - Mulliken, Harral (Box 48, Folder 1802)
  - Mullins, Frederic B. (Box 48, Folder 1803)
  - Munger, George G. (Box 48, Folder 1803)
  - Munger, Raymond Bowen (Box 48, Folder 1803)
  - Munger, Robert Louis (Box 48, Folder 1804)
  - Munger, Theodore Thornton (Box 48, Folder 1804)
  - Munn, John (Box 48, Folder 1805)
  - [?]Munroe, George (Box 48, Folder 1806)
  - Munson, Aeneas (Box 48, Folder 1807)
  - Munson, Charles S. (Box 48, Folder 1808)